{
    "id": "8252c0130fab48a7b841973e937f05e4",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We went out ………………………. the rain.",
            "description": "Write despite or in spite of",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "despite of",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "efeeb51e28344820b6913cf62d2f0449"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is a library …………………………. my house.",
            "description": "We use opposite to indicate position across a road/river.",
            "answers": [
                "in front of",
                "opposite"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eab61bc15f7c445b8b8470bf0afa2799"
        },
        {
            "question": "She died ………………………… receiving the best medical care.",
            "description": "In spite of is the opposite of because of. It is used to introduce an idea that contrasts with the idea mentioned before.",
            "answers": [
                "in spite of",
                "despite of",
                "because of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "afabaf8ff7fb4544bd5924569f5fc128"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was promoted …………………………… his hard work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "because of",
                "in spite of"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f903501ccfb4d51b243f070b4f2a4df"
        },
        {
            "question": "He lost his job ………………………… working very hard.",
            "description": "Despite and in spite of mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "despite",
                "in spite of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f918bfd67c4740c28e25cdc37a470035"
        },
        {
            "question": "We arrive …………………………. Mumbai at midday.",
            "description": "We always write in or at after arrive.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "into",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "acaf1082255b443ea086197c2386d427"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old woman sat down ………………………… the floor.",
            "description": "We use in or on after sit down. On indicates position on the surface.",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "on",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d6fbf9e9524343d9aa34ecf1061753f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "When the princess kissed the frog, it changed ………………………… a handsome prince.",
            "description": "Change is followed by into.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "into",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6e2af6aab15d458c8656e2cdaccf2627"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you translate this report …………………………. German?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "to",
                "into"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "772b387fbdcf4065b933a2e550b355dc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat is ………………………….. the roof.",
            "description": "We use on to indicate position on the surface.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c60a525896a34a8c8e9ae240a3e2aeeb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I usually work from 10 …………………….. six.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "until",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c838b81c5c4f4076867e0d447629fb3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "A sedan can seat ……………………….. five people.",
            "description": "We use up to to talk about quantity.",
            "answers": [
                "until",
                "up to",
                "as far as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2fcadc95ec7d4e04b25d87b016cdf8ca"
        }
    ]
}